Every child needs to feel loved.
The Boy is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by William Brent Bell.
A young American woman takes a job as a nanny in a remote English village, soon discovering that the
family's eight-year-old son is a life-sized doll that comes with a list of strict rules.
Greta Evans, played by Lauren Cohan.
Malcolm, played by Rupert Evans.
Brahms Heelshire, played by James Russell.
Mr. Heelshire, played by Jim Norton.
Mrs. Heelshire, played by Diana Hardcastle.
Cole, played by Ben Robson.
The Boy is a 2016 horror film directed by William
Brent Bell and written by Stacey Menear.
The film stars Lauren Cohan and Rupert Evans.
It is an international co-production between China and the United States.
Filming began on March 10, 2015, in Victoria, British Columbia.
STXfilms released The Boy in the United States on January 22.
The film grossed $64 million worldwide on a $10 million budget.
A sequel, Brahms: The Boy II, was released on February 21, 2020.
The film explores themes of mask, suicide, fire, england, loss of loved one.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.